socialsponder.com 2010-11-29

# Mobile Text, Instant Message, Email, and Mobile Keyword: All-In-One Marketing by StomperQast

StomperQast reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to modify or change this Privacy Policy at any time with or without prior notice to you. You should review the current Privacy Policy on a regular basis. The date of the last update will be posted at the top of this Privacy Policy for your convenience. Your continued use of the StomperQast service following the posting of any changes to the Privacy Policy constitutes your full acceptance of those changes. If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about this Privacy Policy, you may email us at [**sfoster@calmu.edu**](mailto:sfoster@calmu.edu).

## Information Collection / Opt-Out

StomperQast provides its customers (also referred to as "you") the tools and resources to collect your subscribers' contact info on an opt-in basis. Subscribers on the other hand have ability to opt-out of your distribution lists easily and can grant or revoke your ability to view and export their contact information even if they opt-in by signing in at Subscription Management and unchecking "Allow access to my contact information." box. **NOTE:** Receiving mobile text messages from StomperQast is completely FREE of charge; however, standard text messaging rates from wireless providers still apply. **

Online Sign-up

**

StomperQast allows you to collect email addresses, instant message screen names, and mobile phone numbers when subscribers opt-in to join your distribution list(s) via an Online Sign-up page powered by StomperQast . When joining a distribution list, we will ask subscribers for personal information such as their name, mobile phone number, IM screen name, email address, and optional password. The information they provide and the information StomperQast obtains about them may be used to: 

  * Provide subscribers with products and services they request.
  * To anticipate and resolve problems and conflicts with our products and services.
  * For verification and authentication purposes in regards to requests or changes of any personal information or data related.
  * For other purposes communicated to them at the time they provide or authorize the use of their information.

StomperQast provides subscribers the opportunity to opt-in, opt-out or change their settings via a link in the footer of email and IM messages. These options are also made available when subscribers sign in at Subscription Management. 

**Mobile Keyword**

In addition to Online Sign-up pages, you can also collect mobile phone numbers when subscribers text your Mobile Keyword (that you create) to StomperQast 's short code (69302 ). By texting your Mobile Keyword, subscribers are opting-in their mobiles phones to join your distribution list(s). They are also giving implied consent for you to send them text messages and to allow you to view and access their mobile phone numbers. Subscribers can remove their mobile phone numbers from your database at anytime by replying to any text message they receive from StomperQast with "STOP". They can also change permission for you to view (or export) their contact information by unchecking "Allow access to my contact information." box while they are signed in to Subscription Management page. 

## Sharing and Usage / Exporting

StomperQast owns all contact information collected on this site - both your contact information and your subscribers' contact information. A "subscriber" is defined as any person who has opted-in to receive messages from you via an Online Sign-up page or Mobile Keyword.

StomperQast does not share, sell, or rent any contact information with any party unless StomperQast obtains explicit or implied consent from the owners of such contact information. An implied consent is when your subscriber texts your Mobile Keyword to StomperQast 's short code. In this case, your subscriber's phone number may be shared with you. However, if the subscriber signs into his/her own Subscription Management page and unchecks this consent, the contact information will not be viewable or exportable even if you are still able to send messages to the same contact information. An explicit consent is when your subscriber leaves the default setting "Allow [StomperQast user] to access my info." checked at your Online Sign-up page or checks "Allow access to my contact information." option in Subscription Management page.

**NOTE:** Whether explicit or implied, you are not allowed to share your subscribers' contact info with any third party for any reason. Also, StomperQast may use or disclose information, including your personal info and your subscribers' contact info, under the following very limited circumstances: 

  * To enforce our Terms of Use or other legal agreements. 
  * To outsource any of the tasks referenced in this Privacy Policy, such as billing, customer service, or responding to inquiries.
  * In response to a subpoena, court order, or other legal process.
  * To establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * To a company controlled by, or under common control with, StomperQast for any purpose permitted by this Privacy Policy. 
  * When StomperQast believes such use or disclosure is (a) necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities, fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or (b) required by law.
  * In the event of a merger, acquisition, consolidation, divestiture, or bankruptcy of StomperQast.

**NOTE:** The StomperQast service is not intended for children under 13, and StomperQast does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13.
